bp8.hk 2015-03-24

# Privacy | BP8

**Privacy Policy**

**“Bidders’ Paradise (bp8.hk)” is** **committed to respecting your privacy. We** **ha** **ve** **built** **our** **w** **eb site so that, in general, you can visit** **Bidders’ Paradise** **on the** **w** **eb without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with “** **Bidders’ Paradise”** **.**

This statement regarding the privacy of the personally identifiable information you provide online covers four main areas: **Awareness, Choice, Accuracy, Access,** **and** **Security.**

**AWARENESS**

“Bidders’ Paradise” provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**1.** **What we collect.** Upon logging onto our web server, it automatically recognizes your domain name but not your E-mail address (where possible). We will collect the domain name from which you log on, aggregate information on what pages you access or visit, user-specific information on what pages you access or visit and information volunteered by you (such as survey information and/or site registrations).

We do not collect your e-mail address unless you contact us by e-mail or volunteer your e-mail address and other personal information.

We do not collect "cookies" to store your preferences and record session information, such as items you add to your shopping cart.

On some bp8.hk web sites, you can order products or services, make requests and register to receive materials. The types of personal information that may be collected on these pages are name, customer number, contact and billing information, transaction and credit card information.

In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products and contact preferences.

**2\. How we use it.** “Bidders’ Paradise” uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on services and benefits, and to personalize our web sites for you. Credit card and bank account numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes.

**3\. Whom we share it with.**  “Bidders’ Paradise” will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others unless we have your permission. We will only share the personal data you provide online with other “Bidders’ Paradise” entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such “Bidders’ Paradise” entities and/or business partners are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements.

**CHOICE**

“Bidders’ Paradise” will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy.

**ACCURACY & ACCESS **

“Bidders’ Paradise” strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate and secure. We do not provide access to your information online. In order to update or correct your information with “Bidders’ Paradise” it will be necessary for you to contact “Bidders’ Paradise” directly. To protect your privacy and security, upon contacting us we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections.

**SECURITY**

“Bidders’ Paradise” is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use the latest in encryption technology when collecting or transferring sensitive data, such as credit card and bank account information.

**Future Developments.**  From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically. We will only use data collected after a policy has changed for the new purposes.
